West of New City, Orchid Field, Road to Dane Tower and Nyctalinth
Road to Nyctalinth
Road connecting Nyctalinth, Rattkin Ruins and Orkogre Forest
Orkogre Forest
East of New City, Munkharama Bridge, Road to Munkharama and Orkogre Forest
Road from Munkharama to Ukpyr
Road from Ukpyr to Mountains
Mountain Steps
Eryn River
Sea of Sorrows Center
Sea of Sorrows West
Sea of Sorrows East
Sea of Sorrows South
Myrmideon Forest and Lesser Wilds
New City
Dane Tower
Nyctalinth
Beginners Dungeon and Orkogre Castle
Rattkin Ruins
Munkharama and Land of Dreams
Sky City
Ukpyr
Witch Cave, Giants Cave and Sphinx Cave
Munkharama Underground Temple
Crypt (Hall of the Dead and Chamber of Gorrors)
Brombadeg Watery Cave
Astral Dominae Tomb (Teleporter Levels and the Tomb)
High Mountains
Nyctalinth Dungeon
Funhouse
Old City, Abbey Cellar, Mountain Exit from Funhouse, Dane Tower Top Levels (5,6,7 and 8)
New City (T'Rang building, Umpani Building, Security Staion and Mysterious Courtyard)
